Guide to the Time Inc. Subject Files 1889-2015 (bulk 1934-1993) MS 3009-RG 1 MS 3009-RG 1
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Subject Files
1889-2015 (bulk 1934-1993)
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 1
94 Linear feet in 94 record cartons
The Time Inc. Subject Files contain materials that document the history of Time Inc. as an organization, focusing on the areas of corporate, editorial, and publishing. The records cover the various departments, magazines, publishers, and subsidiary corporations that operate under the Time Inc. umbrella. The Time Inc. Archives originally assembled and arranged the Subject Files for use by writers and researchers working on three authorized volumes of Time Inc. history. This record group contains primary documents from throughout the company and contains the majority of early records.
Arrangement Note
The materials within the Time Inc. Subject Files record group are organized into two series: I. 1960 and Before; and II. 1961 and Later. Each series is organized alphabetically by the subject. Subjects with multiple folders are further organized chronologically.
Historical Note
The Time Inc. Archives originally assembled and arranged the Subject Files for use by writers (Robert T. Elson and Curtis Prendergast) and researchers working on three authorized volumes of Time Inc. history: Time Inc.: The Intimate History of a Publishing Enterprise, 1923-1941; The World of Time Inc.: The Intimate History of a Publishing Enterprise, 1941-1960; and The World of Time Inc.: The Intimate History of a Publishing Enterprise, 1960-1980. Elson published the first volume in 1968.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers with the exception of restricted materials. Restricted materials may include privileged attorney correspondence; student records; medical records; personnel performance evaluations; contracts and agreements; and records with personally identifiable information. Unreformatted audiovisual material and digital material in the collection is not accessible. Restricted materials are located in boxes R3 to R5. Materials created within the past 35 years also may be subject to restriction on a case-by-case basis. Materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use.
Related Archival Materials Note
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other records groups and overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library.
Scope and Contents Note
The Time Inc. Subject Files document the history of Time Inc. as an organization and have information on each publication and many departments at Time Inc. This record group contains primary documents from throughout the company and contains the majority of early records.
The materials focus on three main areas: corporate, editorial, and publishing. Corporate covers the acquisition and sale of entities as well as contracts and agreements between organizations, negotiations, board meetings, and other similar business relations. Editorial relates to the work being done by correspondents, reporters, and researchers. Publishing includes everything from advertising and promotion to production and circulation. While the corporate, editorial, and publishing materials are generally separated from each other, there are instances where they are interfiled. The records cover the various departments, magazines, publishers, and subsidiary corporations that operate under the Time Inc. umbrella.
Included among the documents are annual reports, advertisements, affidavits, agendas, agreements, announcements, biographical summaries, briefs, budgets, clippings, codes of conduct, committee reports, congressional bills, contracts, correspondence, cross reference sheets, directories, drafts, emergency instructions, evacuation/disaster preparedness plans, financial studies, floor plans, guidelines, handwritten notes, ID forms, job descriptions, magazines, memoranda, notes, outlines, pamphlets, photos, policies, polls and statistics, posters, press releases, project proposals, promotional materials, public notices, reports, schedules, scripts, sheet music, staff lists, surveys, telegrams, transcripts, transparencies, work flow charts and other documents regarding Time Inc.'s daily workings. Additionally, there are corporate records such as acquisition agreements, board minutes, board reports, bylaws, dissolution forms, escrow agreements, foreign corporation applications, incorporation certificates, liquidation papers, stock certificates, tax returns, trademark certificates, and transfers of title. Folders with later dates contain a higher quantity of newspaper clippings and press releases. Not all folders include materials. Any folders found empty were retained and noted.
Some of the topics covered are the Cold War, contract negotiations, the United States' foreign and domestic policies, the creation of job descriptions, establishment of an employee health care plan and stock options, hiring guidelines, human resources conflicts related to race and gender, internal and external criticisms, intergovernmental relations, the involvement of the magazine and staff in national political campaigns, lawsuits involving Time Inc., magazine censorship, male employee draft status, manpower problems during World War II, participation in the newspaper guild, proposals for new advertising campaigns, regional political and economic developments, and strategies to boost circulation.
Additional records on the divisions, departments and offices at Time Inc. are in Time Inc. Reference Files, MS 3009-RG 3.
Provenance
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Corporation records; Organization files; Corporations -- History; Corporations -- New York (State) -- New York.; Periodicals -- Publishing.; Publishers and publishing -- New York (State) -- New York.; Printing industry; Securities -- Listing.; Time, inc. -- Management; Time, inc. -- Archives; Time, inc. -- History
- Series I: 1960 and Before, 1889-1963; 44 Linear feet (44 boxes)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1930-1935 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 1)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1936-1938 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 2)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 3)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1940: Corporate Journalism: Journalism Campaign (Offsite-box 411, Folder 4-5)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 411)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1941-1942 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1943-1944 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 7)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 8)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1947 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 9)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 10)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1949: Corporate Campaign: Campaign About Advertising (Offsite-box 411, Folder 11)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 12)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1958-1960 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 14)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1952-1957 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 13)
  - Advertising, Corporate: 1951-1960: Advertisers (A-Z) (Offsite-box 411, Folder 15)
  - Architectural Forum: 1932-1934 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 16)
  - Architectural Forum: 1935: Jan-April (Offsite-box 411, Folder 17)
  - Architectural Forum: 1935: May-Dec (Offsite-box 411, Folder 18)
  - Architectural Forum: 1936-1937 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 19)
  - Architectural Forum: 1938 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 20)
  - Architectural Forum: 1938: "Plus" (Offsite-box 411, Folder 21)
  - Architectural Forum: 1939 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 22)
  - Architectural Forum: 1940-1943 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 23)
  - Architectural Forum: 1944-1948 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 24)
  - Architectural Forum: 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 25)
  - Architectural Forum/ House & Home: 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 26)
  - Architectural Forum/ House & Home: 1953 (Offsite-box 411, Folder 27)
  - Architectural Forum/ House & Home: 1954 (Offsite-box 412, Folder 1)
  - Architectural Forum/ House & Home: 1955 (Offsite-box 412, Folder 2)
  - Architectural Forum/ House & Home: 1956: Jan-July (Offsite-box 412, Folder 3)
  - Architectural Forum/ House & Home: 1956: Aug-Dec (Offsite-box 412, Folder 4)
  - Architectural Forum/ House & Home: 1957 (Offsite-box 412, Folder 5)
  - Architectural Forum/ House & Home: 1958 (Offsite-box 412, Folder 6)
  - Architectural Forum/ House & Home: 1959: Jan-May (Offsite-box 412, Folder 7)
  - Architectural Forum/ House & Home: 1959: June-Dec (Offsite-box 412, Folder 8)
  - Architectural Forum/ House & Home: 1960 (Offsite-box 412, Folder 9)
  - Architectural Forum: Building Reporter (Offsite-box 412, Folder 10)
  - Architectural Forum: Index (Offsite-box 412, Folder 11-12)
  - Board of Directors (Offsite-box 412)
  - Board of Directors [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Circulation, Corporate: 1932-1940 (Offsite-box 412, Folder 14)
  - Circulation, Corporate: 1941-1945 (Offsite-box 412, Folder 15)
  - Circulation, Corporate: 1946 (Offsite-box 412, Folder 16)
  - Circulation, Corporate: 1947-1950 (Offsite-box 412, Folder 17)
  - Circulation, Corporate: 1951-1960 (Offsite-box 412, Folder 18)
  - Civil Defense & Disaster Survival: 1941-1960 (Offsite-box 412, Folder 19)
  - Company Services (Offsite-box 412, Folder 20)
  - Corporate Affairs: Washington Representation (Offsite-box 412, Folder 21)
  - Corporate Development: 1930-1940 (Offsite-box 412, Folder 22)
  - Corporate Development: 1941-1943 (Offsite-box 412, Folder 23)
  - Corporate Development: 1944-1950 (Offsite-box 412, Folder 24)
  - Corporate Development: 1951-1959 (Offsite-box 412, Folder 25)
  - Corporate Development: 1960 (Offsite-box 412)
  - Corporate Development: 1960 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Corporate, General (Offsite-box 412, Folder 27)
  - Corporate Secretary: Incorporations: Certificates: 1931-1948 (Offsite-box 412)
  - Corporate Secretary: Incorporations: Certificates: 1931-1948 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Corporate Secretary: Incorporations: Certificates: 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 413)
  - Corporate Secretary: Incorporations: Certificates: 1953-1954 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Corporate Secretary: Incorporations: Contracts: 1931-1943 (Offsite-box 413, Folder 3)
  - Corporate Secretary: Incorporations: Contracts: 1943-1953 (Offsite-box 413, Folder 4)
  - Corporate Secretary: Stock: Common, Class A: 1922-1929 (Offsite-box 413, Folder 5)
  - Corporate Secretary: Stock: Common, Class B: 1922-1929 (Offsite-box 413, Folder 6)
  - Corporate Secretary: Stock: Preferred: 1922-1928 (Offsite-box 413, Folder 7)
  - Corporate Secretary: Stock: Misc: 1922-1928 (Offsite-box 413)
  - Corporate Secretary: Stock: Misc: 1922-1928 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Corporate Secretary: Stock: Misc: 1929-1940 (Offsite-box 413)
  - Corporate Secretary: Stock: Misc: 1929-1940 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Corporate Secretary: Stock: Misc: 1941-1950 (Offsite-box 413)
  - Corporate Secretary: Stock: Misc: 1941-1950 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Corporate Secretary: Stock: Misc: 1951-1960 (Offsite-box 413)
  - Corporate Secretary: Stock: Misc: 1951-1960 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Corporate Secretary: Stockholders Reports: 1922-1960 (Offsite-box 413, Folder 12)
  - Edit: 1928-1934 (Offsite-box 413)
  - Edit: 1928-1934 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Edit: 1935: England (incl. Abdication Crisis) (Offsite-box 413, Folder 14)
  - Edit: 1935: Misc (Offsite-box 413)
  - Edit: 1935: Misc [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Edit: 1936: England (incl. Abdication Crisis) (Offsite-box 413)
  - Edit: 1936: England (incl. Abdication Crisis) [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Edit: 1936: Misc (Offsite-box 413)
  - Edit: 1936: Misc [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Edit: 1937: England (incl. Abdication Crisis) (Offsite-box 413, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1937: Misc (Offsite-box 413)
  - Edit: 1937: Misc [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Edit: 1938: Misc: Jan-April (Offsite-box 413)
  - Edit: 1938: Misc: Jan-April [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Edit: 1938: Misc: May-July (Offsite-box 413, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1938: Misc: Aug-Sept (Offsite-box 414)
  - Edit: 1938: Misc: Aug-Sept [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Edit: 1938: Misc: Oct-Dec (Offsite-box 414)
  - Edit: 1938: Misc: Oct-Dec [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Edit: 1938: Surveys: Time Inc's News Gathering Facilities (Offsite-box 414, Folder 3)
  - Edit: 1939: England (Offsite-box 414, Folder 4)
  - Edit: 1939: Far East (incl. White Cables) (Offsite-box 414, Folder 5)
  - Edit: 1939: Organization (Offsite-box 414, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1939: Misc: Jan-June (Offsite-box 414, Folder 7)
  - Edit: 1939: Misc: July-Dec (Offsite-box 414, Folder 8)
  - Edit: 1940: America: Election: Jan-June (Offsite-box 414, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1940: America: Election: July-Sept (Offsite-box 414, Folder 10)
  - Edit: 1940: America: Election: Oct-Dec (Offsite-box 414, Folder 11)
  - Edit: 1940: America: Misc (Offsite-box 414)
  - Edit: 1940: America: Misc [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Edit: 1940: Organization (Offsite-box 414)
  - Edit: 1940: Organization [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Edit: 1940: Canada (Offsite-box 414, Folder 14)
  - Edit: 1940: Censorship (Offsite-box 414, Folder 15)
  - Edit: 1940: England (Offsite-box 414, Folder 16)
  - Edit: 1940: Far East (Offsite-box 414, Folder 17)
  - Edit: 1940: France (Offsite-box 414, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1940: Latin America (Offsite-box 414, Folder 19)
  - Edit: 1940-1945: Russia (Offsite-box 414, Folder 20)
  - Edit: 1940: Misc: Jan-June (Offsite-box 414, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1940: Misc: July-Dec (Offsite-box 414, Folder 22)
  - Edit: 1941: "American Century": Published Materials (Offsite-box 414, Folder 23-25)
  - Edit: 1941: "American Century": Misc (Offsite-box 414, Folder 26)
  - Edit: 1941: Canada (Offsite-box 414, Folder 27)
  - Edit: 1941: Censorship (Offsite-box 414, Folder 28)
  - Edit: 1941: America (Offsite-box 414, Folder 29)
  - Edit: 1941: England (Offsite-box 414, Folder 30)
  - Edit: 1941: Far East: Misc (Offsite-box 414, Folder 31)
  - Edit: 1941: Far East: Jacoby's Cables (Offsite-box 415, Folder 1)
  - Edit: 1941: Far East: Mydan's Cables (Offsite-box 415, Folder 2)
  - Edit: 1941: Far East: White's Cables (Offsite-box 415, Folder 3)
  - Edit: 1941: Germany (Offsite-box 415, Folder 4)
  - Edit: 1941: Latin America (incl. Chilean Incident) (Offsite-box 415, Folder 5)
  - Edit: 1941: Girand Rifle Controversy (Offsite-box 415, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1941: Zam Zam Episode (Offsite-box 415, Folder 7)
  - Edit: 1941: Organization (Offsite-box 415)
  - Edit: 1941: Organization [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Edit: 1941: Misc (Offsite-box 415, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1941: "First Thirty Hours" (Offsite-box 415, Folder 10)
  - Edit: 1941: Russia (Offsite-box 415, Folder 11)
  - Edit: 1942: America: Economics (Culminating F, 12/42 "Domestic Economy") (Offsite-box 415, Folder 12)
  - Edit: 1942: Far East: Jacoby Dinner (Offsite-box 415, Folder 13)
  - Edit: 1942: America: Misc (Offsite-box 415, Folder 14)
  - Edit: 1942: Censorship (Offsite-box 415, Folder 15-16)
  - Edit: 1942: England: Postwar Dept. Supplement: F, 5/42 Relations with Britain (Offsite-box 415, Folder 17)
  - Edit: 1942: England (Offsite-box 415, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1942: Far East: Jan-July (Offsite-box 415, Folder 19)
  - Edit: 1942: Far East: Aug-Dec (Offsite-box 415, Folder 20)
  - Edit: 1942: Geopolitics (Offsite-box 415, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1942: Latin America (Offsite-box 415, Folder 22)
  - Edit: 1942: Russia (Offsite-box 415, Folder 23)
  - Edit: 1942: Misc (Offsite-box 415-416)
  - Edit: 1942: Misc [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Edit: 1942: Organization (Offsite-box 416, Folder 2-3)
  - Edit: 1943: America (Offsite-box 416, Folder 4-5)
  - Edit: 1943: Canada (Offsite-box 416, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1943-1963: Censorship (Offsite-box 416)
  - Edit: 1943-1963: Censorship [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Edit: 1943: Latin America (Offsite-box 416, Folder 8)
  - Edit: 1943: England (Offsite-box 416, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1943: Organization (Time Inc.) (Offsite-box 416, Folder 10-11)
  - Edit: 1943: "Public Opinion" Dept (Offsite-box 416, Folder 12)
  - Edit: 1943: Russia (Offsite-box 416, Folder 13)
  - Edit: 1943: Misc: Jan-June (Offsite-box 416, Folder 14-15)
  - Edit: 1943: Misc: July-Dec (Offsite-box 416, Folder 16-17)
  - Edit: 1944: America: Jan-April (Offsite-box 416, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1944: America: May-Aug (Offsite-box 416, Folder 19)
  - Edit: 1944: America: Sept-Oct (Offsite-box 416, Folder 20)
  - Edit: 1944: America: Nov-Dec (Offsite-box 416, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1944: Balkan States (Offsite-box 416, Folder 22)
  - Edit: 1944: England (Offsite-box 416, Folder 23)
  - Edit: 1944: Far East: China: Jan-May (Offsite-box 416, Folder 24)
  - Edit: 1944: Far East: China: June-Oct (Offsite-box 416, Folder 25)
  - Edit: 1944: Far East: China: Nov-Dec (Offsite-box 416, Folder 26)
  - Edit: 1944: Far East: Misc (Offsite-box 417, Folder 1)
  - Edit: 1944: Invasion Coverage: Jan-May (Offsite-box 417, Folder 2)
  - Edit: 1944: Invasion Coverage: June (Offsite-box 417, Folder 3)
  - Edit: 1944: Invasion Coverage: July-Dec (Offsite-box 417, Folder 4)
  - Edit: 1944: Organization (Time Inc.) (Offsite-box 417, Folder 5-6)
  - Edit: 1944: "Public Opinion" Dept (Offsite-box 417, Folder 7)
  - Edit: 1944: Russia (Offsite-box 417, Folder 8)
  - Edit: 1944: Misc (Offsite-box 417, Folder 9-10)
  - Edit: 1945: Misc: Jan-June (Offsite-box 417, Folder 11)
  - Edit: 1945: Misc: July-Dec (Offsite-box 417, Folder 12)
  - Edit: 1945: Far East: China: Jan-Oct (Offsite-box 417, Folder 13-14)
  - Edit: 1945: Far East: China: Nov-Dec (Offsite-box 417, Folder 15-16)
  - Edit: 1945: America (Offsite-box 417, Folder 17)
  - Edit: 1945: Canada (Offsite-box 417, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1945: Dumbarton Oaks & San Francisco (UN) (Offsite-box 417, Folder 19-20)
  - Edit: 1945: Far East: Misc (Offsite-box 417, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1945: Latin America (Offsite-box 417, Folder 22)
  - Edit: 1945: Organization (Offsite-box 417, Folder 23)
  - Edit: 1947: Organization (Offsite-box 2220, Folder 1)
  - Edit: 1945: "Public Opinion Dept" (Offsite-box 418, Folder 1)
  - Edit: 1945: Russia (Offsite-box 418, Folder 2)
  - Edit: 1946: America (Offsite-box 418, Folder 3)
  - Edit: 1946: Far East: China (Offsite-box 418, Folder 4-5)
  - Edit: 1946: Latin America (Offsite-box 418, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1946: Middle East (Offsite-box 418, Folder 7)
  - Edit: 1946: Organization (Offsite-box 418, Folder 8)
  - Edit: 1946: Russia (Offsite-box 418, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1946: Newsbureau Activities Report (Offsite-box 418, Folder 10)
  - Edit: 1946: Newsbureau Usage Survey (Offsite-box 418, Folder 11-13)
  - Edit: 1946: Misc (Offsite-box 418, Folder 14-15)
  - Edit: 1947: America (Offsite-box 418, Folder 16)
  - Edit: 1947: Far East: China (Offsite-box 418, Folder 17-18)
  - Edit: 1947: Far East: Misc (Offsite-box 418, Folder 19)
  - Edit: 1947: Latin America: Argentina (Offsite-box 418, Folder 20)
  - Edit: 1947: Latin America: Brazil (Offsite-box 418, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1947: Latin America: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 418, Folder 22)
  - Edit: 1947: Organization (Offsite-box 418, Folder 23)
  - Edit: 1947: Russia (Offsite-box 419, Folder 1)
  - Edit: 1947: Misc (Offsite-box 419, Folder 2-3)
  - Edit: 1948: America (Offsite-box 419, Folder 4)
  - Edit: 1948: Russia (Offsite-box 419, Folder 5)
  - Edit: 1948: Organization (Time Inc.) (Offsite-box 419, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1948: Misc (Offsite-box 419, Folder 7-8)
  - Edit: 1948: Far East (Offsite-box 419, Folder 9-10)
  - Edit: 1948: Latin America (Offsite-box 419, Folder 11)
  - Edit: 1948: Middle East (Offsite-box 419, Folder 12)
  - Edit: 1949: America (Offsite-box 419, Folder 13)
  - Edit: 1949: Far East (Offsite-box 419, Folder 14-15)
  - Edit: 1949: Misc: June-Dec (Offsite-box 419, Folder 16)
  - Edit: 1949: Latin America (Offsite-box 419, Folder 17)
  - Edit: 1949: Organization (Time Inc.) (Offsite-box 419, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1949: Misc: Jan-May (Offsite-box 419, Folder 19)
  - Edit: 1950: America (Offsite-box 419, Folder 20)
  - Edit: 1950: Far East: China (Offsite-box 419, Folder 21-22)
  - Edit: 1950: Far East: Korea (Offsite-box 419, Folder 23-24)
  - Edit: 1950: Far East: Misc (Offsite-box 419, Folder 25)
  - Edit: 1950: Latin America (Offsite-box 419, Folder 26)
  - Edit: 1950: Middle East (Offsite-box 419, Folder 27)
  - Edit: 1950: Organization (Time Inc.) (Offsite-box 419, Folder 28)
  - Edit: 1950: Misc (Offsite-box 420, Folder 1-2)
  - Edit: 1951: America (Offsite-box 420, Folder 3)
  - Edit: 1951: England (Offsite-box 420, Folder 4)
  - Edit: 1951: Far East (Offsite-box 420, Folder 5-6)
  - Edit: 1951: Latin America (Offsite-box 420, Folder 7)
  - Edit: 1951: Mid East (Offsite-box 420, Folder 8)
  - Edit: 1951: Organization (Offsite-box 420, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1951: Misc (Offsite-box 420, Folder 10)
  - Edit: 1952: America (Offsite-box 420, Folder 11-12)
  - Edit: 1952: England (Offsite-box 420, Folder 13)
  - Edit: 1952: Far East (Offsite-box 420, Folder 14)
  - Edit: 1952: Organization (Offsite-box 420, Folder 15)
  - Edit: 1952: Misc (Offsite-box 420, Folder 16)
  - Edit: 1953: America (Offsite-box 420, Folder 17)
  - Edit: 1953: England (Offsite-box 420, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1953: Far East: Korea (Offsite-box 420, Folder 19)
  - Edit: 1953: Far East: Vietnam (Offsite-box 420, Folder 20)
  - Edit: 1953: Far East: Misc (Offsite-box 420, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1953: Italy (Offsite-box 420, Folder 22)
  - Edit: 1953: Middle East (Offsite-box 420, Folder 23)
  - Edit: 1953: Misc (Offsite-box 420, Folder 24-25)
  - Edit: 1953: Organization (Offsite-box 420, Folder 26)
  - Edit: 1953: Russia (Offsite-box 420, Folder 27)
  - Edit: 1954: America (Offsite-box 420, Folder 28)
  - Edit: 1954: Far East (Offsite-box 420, Folder 29)
  - Edit: 1954: Foreign Policy Appraisal: July (Offsite-box 420-421)
  - Edit: 1954: Foreign Policy Appraisal: Aug. (Offsite-box 421, Folder 2-3)
  - Edit: 1954: Hydrogen Bomb & Oppenheimer Case: Publicity (Offsite-box 421, Folder 4-5)
  - Edit: 1954: Hydrogen Bomb & Oppenheimer Case: Misc (Offsite-box 421, Folder 6-7)
  - Edit: 1954: Italy (Offsite-box 421, Folder 8)
  - Edit: 1954: Mideast (Offsite-box 421, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1954: Misc (Offsite-box 421, Folder 10-11)
  - Edit: 1954: Organization (Offsite-box 421, Folder 12)
  - Edit: 1954: World Economic Program (Offsite-box 421, Folder 13)
  - Edit: 1955: Far East: Jan-Apr (Offsite-box 421, Folder 14)
  - Edit: 1955: Far East: May-Dec (Offsite-box 421, Folder 15)
  - Edit: 1955: Italy (Offsite-box 421, Folder 16)
  - Edit: 1955: Mideast (Offsite-box 421, Folder 17)
  - Edit: 1955: Russia (Offsite-box 421, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1955: South America (Offsite-box 421, Folder 19)
  - Edit: 1956: America (Offsite-box 421, Folder 20)
  - Edit: 1956: Cancer Cigarette Issue (Offsite-box 421, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1956: Far East: China Visas For Newsmen (Offsite-box 421, Folder 22)
  - Edit: 1956: Far East: Misc (Offsite-box 421, Folder 23-24)
  - Edit: 1956: Hungary (Offsite-box 421-422)
  - Edit: 1956: Italy (Offsite-box 422, Folder 2)
  - Edit: 1956: Latin America (Offsite-box 422, Folder 3)
  - Edit: 1956: Mideast (Offsite-box 422, Folder 4-5)
  - Edit: 1956: Organization (Offsite-box 422, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1956: Russia (Offsite-box 422, Folder 7)
  - Edit: 1956: South America (Offsite-box 422, Folder 8)
  - Edit: 1956: Misc (Offsite-box 422, Folder 9-10)
  - Edit: 1957: America (Offsite-box 422, Folder 11)
  - Edit: 1957: Cancer Cigarette Issue (Offsite-box 422, Folder 12)
  - Edit: China Visas For Newsmen (Offsite-box 422, Folder 13)
  - Edit: 1957: Far East: Misc (Offsite-box 422, Folder 14)
  - Edit: 1957: Latin America (Offsite-box 422, Folder 15)
  - Edit: 1957: Mideast (Offsite-box 422, Folder 16)
  - Edit: 1957: Organization (Offsite-box 422, Folder 17)
  - Edit: 1957: Misc (Offsite-box 422, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1958-1959: Art (Offsite-box 422, Folder 19)